(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-26T21:48:31.414738",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
BIRTH DAY FESTIVAL
BIRTHDAY FESTIVAL
Juice=Juice / S/mileage / Morning Musume. / Berryz Kobo / °C-ute
Morning Musume.
Ah!
Oh!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Yeah!
Hey! Every time I'm so proud of you
Touch my heart! & Touch me please!
もっと近づいてほしい
I want you to get closer to me,
どんなことも
no matter what it is...
話してほしいのよ
...I want you to tell me!
Touch my heart! & Touch me please!
できそうもないくらいなこと
Even if it seems impossible,
おねだりしてくれていいよ
it's okay to beg me for it.
ずっと憧れてた人と
With the person I've always admired...
再会した
...I finally reunited.
運命感じなきゃ
If I don't feel destiny,
嘘だよ
it must be a lie!
Now! Touch my heart
100年たって地球が変わっても
Even if 100 years pass and the Earth changes,
気持ちはかわらないわ
my feelings will never change!
愛の園
Our garden of love!
Now! Touch my heart
明日になって
Tomorrow...
私が邪魔ならば
...if I become a bother,
良い子の私はバイバイ
the good girl in me will say bye bye.
Hey! Every time I’m so proud of you
Touch my heart! And touch me, please!
もっと意地悪でいいよ
It's okay to be more mischievous.
過去も未来も あなたの自由でしょ
Both the past and the future are your freedom, right?
Touch my heart! And touch me, please!
夢は夢と言うの？
Are dreams just dreams?
あなたの夢を知りたい
I want to know your dreams.
ずっと忘れない夜が続いているわ
The nights I'll never forget continue.
運命抱きしめて眠るわ
I'll embrace fate and fall asleep!
千年経って宇宙で暮らしても
Even if a thousand years pass and we live in space,
私は変わらないわ 愛の園
I will not change, it's the garden of love!
明日になって私が邪魔ならば
If I become a bother tomorrow,
良い子の私はバイバイ
the good girl in me will say bye bye.
Bye-bye
Let's go!
One!
Two!
One, two,
one!
千年経って宇宙で暮らしても
Even if a thousand years pass and we live in space,
私は変わらないわ 愛 of 園
I will not change, it's the garden of love!
明日になって私が邪魔ならば
If I become a bother tomorrow,
良い子の私はバイバイ
the good girl in me will say bye bye.
Bye-bye
Hey! Every time I’m so proud of you
Kiara-ki! Hi!
I am Takanashi Kiara from holoLive English -Myth-!
And welcome to my birthday 3D live today!
The first song was an iconic, relatively old song from Morning Musume called "Ai no Sono".
Yay! Did you like it?
There was like some funny moves. It's just like... what am I? Haha.
Yay! So, as you can see, today once again, I'm doing a Hello! Project cover song birthday festival.
It's my second time to do like a Hello! Project cover song themed Live.
Did you watch the last one? I hope you did.
And back then, there were a bunch of songs that I felt like, "Ah, I still want to do so badly!" And that's why we're here today.
And, yeah, so a lot of Hello! Project songs to look forward to.
Also, ta-da! #KiaraBday2026,
please use it!
Make me famous!
Take some screenshots,
some clips,
tell the internet about this, what's happening here!
Um, also let's talk a little bit about the background.
What is this? You might wonder.
If you have watched a lot of Hello! Project music videos in your life, you might actually recognize this,
because it's from a Morning Musume song, like, inspired from the music video.
Um, maybe an upcoming song? Maybe after this?
So, we will have corners today!
We are starting right now with the Morning Musume corner,
and then we'll have other corners too, that are all dedicated to my favorite Hello! Project groups.
And, for each corner, there will be like a representative backdrop,
like this one.
So, please pay attention to the different variations of the stages today.
Mhm!
And now I'm kind of sad, because I danced all alone, and I want some friends to come and help me perform.
So, shall we begin and continue with the next song?
Yes, yes!
Bring in the ladies!
カモン！
Come on!
泣いちゃうかも
[Song: I Might Cry]
笑った顔をして返事した
You smiled as you answered me,
あなたが嘘をつく合図だね
that's a sign that you're lying.
二年目の記念日を前にして
With our second anniversary just ahead,
私がフラれちゃって終わるのね
it seems I'll be the one dumped in the end.
「また一人ぼっち」と
“I'll be all alone again,”
自分に言い聞かす私
I tell myself.
気づかないフリをしていつまでも
I wonder if I should pretend not to notice
抱きしめられていようかな
and just let you hold me forever.
ああ あなたが優しいのわかってる
Ah, I know you're being kind,
けどその分つらすぎるの
but that just makes it so much more painful.
お祈りをしたけれど
I prayed and wished,
心は遠く離れてゆく
but our hearts only drift further apart.
ああ 私からお別れ告げようと
Ah, I thought of saying goodbye first,
そう思ったけどできない
but I just can't bring myself to do it.
会話の中で何度も
Time and time again during our conversation,
タイミング見てたけど
I looked for the right moment...
泣いちゃうかも
But I might cry...
I might cry...
泣いちゃうかも
かも かも かも かも
Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe...
どうしてそんな風に無理するの
Why are you forcing yourself like that?
いやならお別れを言ってよね
If you don't like it, just say goodbye.
わざとワガママをしてみたけど
I tried acting selfish on purpose,
優しく笑顔で答える人
but you only responded with a gentle smile.
「もうこれでいいの？」と
“Is this really okay?”
自問自答をする私
I ask myself.
最後だって言う前に抱きしめて
Hold me tight before you say it's over,
ねえねえ冷たくていいから
hey, even a cold embrace is fine.
そのあなたの優しさが罪なのよ
That kindness of yours is criminal,
ほら決心が鈍くなる
look, my resolve is only weakening.
出会った頃みたいに
Just like when we first met,
毎日確かめ合いたい
I want us to confirm our love every day.
ああ もう少しこのままいたいけど
Ah, I want to stay like this a little longer,
そう あなたといたいけれど
yes, I want to be with you, but...
最後の夜が来たら
If our last night comes,
強気なフリしながら
while pretending to be strong...
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry...
かも かも かも かも
Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe...
そのあなたの優しさが罪なのよ
That kindness of yours is criminal,
ほら決心が鈍くなる
look, my resolve is only weakening.
出会った頃みたいに
Just like when we first met,
毎日確かめ合いたい
I want us to confirm our love every day.
ああ もう少しこのままいたいけど
Ah, I want to stay like this a little longer,
そう あなたといたいけれど
yes, I want to be with you, but...
最後の夜が来たら
If our last night comes,
強気なフリしながら
while pretending to be strong...
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry...
かも かも かも かも
Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe...
早く
Hurry...
会いたいよ
I want to see you.
ねえ
Hey...
早く
Hurry...
あなたに会いたい
I want to see you.
YA-HEY HO
色っぽい じれったい
[Song: Sexy Impatient]
YA-HEY HO
ヘイヤ ホエオー
Heya, Hoe-oh
先に 向かってる ROAD
The road ahead...
止まらない ミュージック
the music that doesn't stop.
恋人からの 花束
Bouquet from my lover,
真夜中 届く メール
e-mail arriving at midnight.
女の子なら 誰でも 思う
If I'm a girl, anyone would think:
HAPPY END STORY
やさしく されりゃ うれしい けど
It's nice to be treated gently, but...
限りなく 求めちゃう
I want more without limit.
色っぽい キューピッド
Sexy Cupid,
じれったい キス もっと
teasing, kiss me more.
熱い 鼓動の SEXY ISLAND
Sexy Island of hot heartbeats.
笑ってる 星も
The smiling stars,
気取ってる 午後も
and the pretentious afternoon...
この愛を 見届けて
I want them to witness this love...
欲しい
I want them to.
ヘイヤ ホエオー
Heya, Hoe-oh
海が 輝いて ジェラシー
The shining sea brings jealousy,
独り言の 週末
on this weekend of talking to myself.
あなたと いたなら うれしい
If I were with you, I would be happy.
不思議な 匂い SWEETIE
Mysterious scent, SWEETIE.
寂しい 夜と 楽しい 時間
Lonely nights and fun times...
HAPPY END STORY
もう一度 言うわ 大好きです
I'll say it again, I love you.
抱きしめて 離さないで
Hold me, don't let me go.
色っぽい ビスケット
Sexy biscuit,
じれったい ミス ショット
frustrating, a missed shot.
ずっと 続くの SEXY ISLAND
Sexy Island that continues forever.
愛して 急接近
Love me, rapid approach,
未来に 大接近
big approach to the future.
どこまでも 抱きしめて
I want you to hold me everywhere...
欲しい
I want you to.
色っぽい キューピッド
Sexy Cupid,
じれったい キス もっと
teasing, kiss me more.
熱い 鼓動の SEXY ISLAND
Sexy Island of hot heartbeats.
笑ってる 星も
The smiling stars,
気気取ってる 午後も
and the pretentious afternoon...
この愛を 見届けて
I want them to witness this love...
欲しい
I want them to.
色っぽい ビスケット
Sexy biscuit,
じれったい ミス ショット
frustrating, a missed shot.
ずっと 続くの SEXY ISLAND
Sexy Island that continues forever.
愛して 急接近
Love me, rapid approach,
未来に 大接近
big approach to the future.
どこまでも 抱きしめて
I want you to hold me everywhere...
欲しい
I want you to.
ヘイヤ ホエオー
Heya, Hoe-oh
Isaki Riona
Koganei Niko
Mizumiya Su
Rindo Chihaya
Kikirara Vivi
渋谷を 歩く
I walk around Shibuya...
一人で 歩く
I walk alone... ...
人ごみの 中
In the crowd,
大好きな あの人 探す
looking for the person I love.
大好きなあの人探す
I search for the person I love.
手を繋ぎたい その思いから
I want to hold hands, because of that feeling...
わざと外れてみただけなの
...I purposely strayed, I just tried.
泣きそう こんな私を
I feel like crying. Please don't...
どうか離さないでね
...let go of me.
恋する想いが
The feeling of love...
大きく膨らみ
...swells up big.
考え過ぎたら
If I think too much...
空回りしちゃうな
...I end up spinning my wheels.
まだまだ私は
I'm still...
あなたが怖いわ
...afraid of you.
きっといつの日か
I'm sure one day...
嫌われちゃいそうで
...you'll end up hating me.
あぁ
Ah...
あなたを見つけ
I found you...
涙が出ちゃった
...and tears came out.
少し前から
You'd noticed me...
私に気づいてたなんて
...a while ago?
少しズルいよ
That's kind of sly...
だけど言えない
...but I can't say that.
最初のキッカケは私だし
I was the one who started it...
どうしよう
...so what should I do?
うつむいてたら
As I was looking down...
手を握ってくれたわ
...you held my hand.
大人になっても
Even when we grow up...
もっとその先も
...and even further beyond that.
腰が曲がっても
Even if our waists bend...
手を繋ぐときには
...when we hold hands,
ドキドキするでしょ
...I'll still be excited, won't I?
恥ずかしいでしょ
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
それでも私を
But please gently hold me...
優しく包んでね
...all the same.
あぁ
Ah...
大人になっても
Even when we grow up...
もっとその先も
...and even further beyond that.
腰が曲がっても
Even if our waists bend...
手を繋ぐときには
...when we hold hands,
ドキドキするでしょ
...I'll still be excited, won't I?
恥ずかしいでしょ
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
それでも私を
But please gently hold me...
優しく包んでね
...all the same.
あぁ
Ah...
涙の色
[Song: The Color of Tears]
強情
Stubborn...
あなたは強情
...you're so stubborn,
わからずやのままでね
you're still clueless.
もう付き合いきれない
Enough is enough,
サヨナラ愛し人
goodbye, my love.
友情
Friendship...
「友達」なんて戻れるわけないでしょう
...there's no way we can go back to being "friends," right?
この先もわがままに
You intend to be selfish from this point on too,
振り回すつもり
and keep jerking me around.
浮気なら
If you were cheating...
それなりに許すつもりだった
...I intended to forgive you for that.
プライドを
But I can't forgive you...
傷つけたあの日は許せない
...for the day that you hurt my pride.
涙 止まらぬ涙
Tears, my tears that won't stop,
これですきっとするわ
this will refresh me.
あなたを信じてた
That day I believed you...
あの日がもったいない
...was such a waste.
わぁ...
Ah...
それでも愛してた あなたとのサヨナラ
But I still loved you, our goodbye...
土曜
Saturday...
心の隙間 風を引きそうだけど
It feels like a draft is blowing through my heart...
それならすぐ直るし
But a cold like that will heal quickly.
サヨナラ 愛しい人
Goodbye, my dear.
薄情者と言われても
Even if you call me heartless...
ヨリを戻さないから
I won't get back together with you.
もう電話は出ないわ
I won't answer your calls anymore...
どんなに淋しくても
no matter how lonely I get.
いつもより早いけど
It's earlier than usual, but...
ベッドに入るわ
I'm going to bed.
懐かしい記憶と
With nostalgic memories...
戦いの時間 あぁ
it's time for a battle, ah...
涙 思い出 涙
Tears, memories, tears...
悲しくなんかないよ
I'm not sad at all.
私も50歩100歩ね
I guess we're both in the same boat...
今頃そう思う わぁ
that's what I think now, ah...
あんなに愛してた
I loved you so much...
あなたとのサヨナラ
our goodbye.
涙 止まらない 涙
Tears, I can't stop my tears...
これでスッキリするわ
but this will make me feel refreshed.
あなたを信じてた
I believed in you...
あの日は戻らない あぁ
those days won't return, ah...
涙 思い出 涙
Tears, memories, tears...
悲しくなんかないよ
I'm not sad at all.
私も50歩100歩ね
I guess we're both in the same boat...
今頃そう思う わぁ
that's what I think now, ah...
あんなに愛してた
I loved you so much...
あなたとのサヨナラ あぁ
our goodbye, ah...
あんなに愛してた
I loved you so much...
あなたとのサヨナラ
our goodbye.
イェーイ！お疲れ様でした！
Yay! Great job, everyone!
ようこそようこそ！
Welcome, welcome!
イェーイ！
Yay!
That was Forever Love and Namida no Iro with Flow Glow!
イェーイ！ありがとうございました！
Yay! Thank you so much!
すごい！もうFlow Glowの一員になったみたいな感じですね！
Wow! I feel like I've become a member of Flow Glow!
いやめっちゃ嬉しいです！こんなに大人数で踊れて！
I'm so happy! Being able to dance with so many of us!
まずは自己紹介をみんなに英語でやってもらおうかな！
First, let's have everyone do their self-introductions in English!
えー！英語？ヤバい、できるかな？
What?! In English? Oh no, can we do it?
インターナショナル！頑張ろう！順番は任せますけど。
International! Let's do our best! I'll leave the order to you.
お、じゃあいつもの順番で！英語だけどバリバリね！
Oh, then let's go in the usual order! Give it your all, even if it's in English!
オッケー！
Okay!
Hello everyone! My name is Riona! I'm Flow Glow leader purple purple! Yay! Nice to meet you!
オッケー！おー完璧！
Okay! Wow, perfect!
あー！にこちゃん！にこちゃん落ち着いて！
Ah! Niko-chan! Niko-chan, calm down!
にこちゃん落ち着いて... 落ち着いて！
Niko-chan, calm down... Calm down!
My name is Koganei Niko. Flow Glow's comedian modoki. Yay!
英語がちょっと足りないけど...
My English is a little lacking, but...
はい！しゅぴしゅぴわー！Vroom car, Mizu-Mizu, yay!
Yes! Shupi-shupi-wa! Vroom car, Mizu-Mizu, yay!
Mizu-Mizu! Yes! Vroom vroom! Vroom vroom vroom! Kiara-san! Kiara-san!
Kiara-san, Nihongo no "ookii" wa, eigo de small... small, no?
Kiara-san, does Japanese "ookii" mean "small" in English? No?
Big! Big! Ah, big, big, big!
Big car, Mizu-Mizu! Thank you! Night night!
わかったと思って言ってる？さすがに分かったか！
Did you say that thinking you understood? I guess you got it!
はい、次！
Okay, next!
Hi! Flow Glow DJ and driver, Rindou Chihaya!
プップップッ、ギャルピース！
Puff, puff, puff... Gyarupi!
ギャルピー！
Gyarupi!
ビッグターキー！
Big turkey!
ビーフ、ビッグビーフ！
Beef, big beef!
ピンクターキー、ピンクビーフ。
Pink turkey, pink beef.
はい、せーの、うーー、プフィー！
Okay, ready, set, go... Puffey!
あ、アイムすげえよ、キキララビビデ！
Ah, I'm so amazing, Kiki Rara Bibide!
すげえよ！すげえよ！
Amazing! So amazing!
「すげえよ」って言うのはそんな共通認識じゃないかも...
That "amazing" part might not be common knowledge...
Well, when I chose to do these songs, I really wanted to bring in Flow Glow, because I know they're all really good at dancing.
Yeah, and performing. みんなパフォーマンス上手いから、絶対Flow Glow誘うと完成度高いと思って。
Yeah, and performing. Since everyone performs so well, I thought inviting Flow Glow would make the quality super high.
ありがとう！うれしい！
Thank you! We're so happy!
でも、でも、あの、なんか困ったこととか、難しかった振りとか何かありましたか？
But, but... did you have any trouble or difficult choreography?
全部！全部！全部難しかった！
Everything! Everything! Everything was difficult!
え、でもカッコよかった！みんな、なんかリハーサルの見たときとか、めっちゃカッコいいってなりました。
But it was so cool! When we watched the rehearsals, we were like, "That's so cool!"
私も、なんか、そのみんなでどんどん出来上がって、完成度が高くなっていくうちに...
Me too. As we all gradually put it together and the quality got higher...
もう幸せすぎて、みんなカッコいいって言ってくれて嬉しかった。
I was just so happy, and I was glad everyone said we were cool.
なんかカノンで、結構交互の振りみたいなのが...
In the canon part, there was a lot of alternating choreography...
そういうの今まであんまりなかったから、キアラ先輩に呼んでもらってそれが出来て、嬉しかったです！
We haven't really done things like that before, so I was really happy that Kiara-senpai invited us and we got to do it!
そうね。なんか、あの順番で回るとか、結構多くて。大変でした。まぁ、すみません、難しい振り付け。あの...
Right. Like, there were a lot of times we rotated in order. It was tough. Well, sorry about the difficult choreography. Um...
皆さんのこのコーナーは、℃-uteのコーナーであって。℃-uteっていうグループはダンスがマジでいつも難しいです。
Your corner was the ℃-ute corner. And ℃-ute's dances are seriously always difficult.
確かに、実力派。
Indeed, they're highly skilled.
ご、ごめんね。でもみんな、よく出来てた！
S-sorry about that. But everyone did so well!
℃-uteと言えば、I want to know everybody's favorite Hello! Project song. ハロプロの好きな曲、知りたいけど...
Speaking of ℃-ute, I want to know everyone's favorite Hello! Project song. I want to know your favorite Hello Project songs...
じゃあ、まず、すーちゃんありますか？
First, Su-chan, do you have one?
オラは「おれ」！
I like "Ore"!
おー、いい、全然最近の曲ですね。いいですね。
Oh, nice, that's a really recent song. Nice.
あと、にこちゃんは？
How about Niko-chan?
にこちゃんは...
Niko-chan is...
「バカヤロー！おんなじ気分、だいたいおんなじに生きてやる！」
"You idiot, the same feeling, mostly the same, I'm gonna live!"
が大好きです！
...I love that one!
大好き！いいよね。すごくキャラらしい。
I love it! It's so good. It really suits your character.
わかる。と、結構オタクと聞いて...
I get it. And I heard you're quite an otaku...
そう、私の大好きな曲は、モーニング娘。'14さんの『時空を超え 宇宙を超え』
Yes, my favorite song is Morning Musume。'14's "Toki wo Koe Sora wo Koe".
あ！超名曲！名曲！『時空を超え 宇宙を超え』ってすごい...
Ah! Super masterpiece! Masterpiece! "Toki wo Koe Sora wo Koe" is amazing...
すごい、カッコいいしっとりした曲。
...It's a really cool, beautiful, gentle song.
すごいいいですよね。
It's really good, isn't it?
あと、スマイレージさんは『ぁまのじゃく』。そう、あの、ぁまのじゃく...
Also, for S/mileage, "Amanojaku". Yeah, "Amanojaku"...
ぁまのじゃく！ぁまのじゃくは去年やってたんですよ！
Amanojaku! We did Amanojaku last year!
そう！ぁまのじゃく大好きです！
Yes! I love Amanojaku!
おー、なるほど。はー、詳しそうですね。オタクだね。りこちゃんはどの曲が？
Oh, I see. Wow, you seem to know a lot. Quite an otaku. Riko-chan, which song is yours?
私はあの、『ソラシドねえねえ』が...
For me, it's "Solasi Do ~Nee Nee~"...
初めて聴いたときにめっちゃ素敵な曲だなと思って、超好き。
When I first heard it, I thought it was such a wonderful song, and I love it so much.
Buono!ですね。それもBuono!。みんな大好きなBuono!ですね。わかる。
That's Buono! That's also Buono! Everyone's beloved Buono! I get it.
と、ビビは？
And, Vivi?
はい、ビビは『チュッ！夏パ〜ティ』！キアラ先輩と一緒に『チュッ！』ってしたいわー！
Yes, Vivi is "Chu! Natsu Party"! I want to do 'Chu!' with Kiara-senpai!
ちょっと、やめてー！
Wait, stop it!
キアラ先輩、騙されないでください。
Kiara-senpai, please don't be fooled.
騙されてないよー！可愛いけども。
I'm not fooled! Though it's cute.
この、いろんな曲名を聞くだけで、このライブ、ハロプロカバーソングライブ、何度も何度もやりたいですけど...
Just hearing all these song titles makes me want to do this Hello Project Cover Song Live over and over again, but...
とりあえずは、あの、まだまだあります！℃-uteの次には他のパートも、他のグループもありますので...
For now, there is still more to come! After ℃-ute, we have other parts and other groups...
えー、次のパートに行きましょう！Flow Glowのみんな、ありがとう！
So, let's move on to the next part! Flow Glow everyone, thank you!
ということで、Let's go to the next corner!
And so, Let's go to the next corner!
スマイレージ
Smileage
戌神ころね
Inugami Korone
兎田ぺこら
Usada Pekora
ワトソン・アメリア
Watson Amelia
スマイレージ
Smileage
Wahoo!
Wow wow wow
いまだかつてないような
It's like nothing I've ever experienced before
キラキラした毎日
Every day is sparkling
ぶっちゃけ有頂天な日々送ってる
Frankly, each day is ecstatic
Wow wow wow
恋をしたら勉強が
After I fell in love, my studies
手につかない毎日
Every day, I can't focus on them
恋のせいにしちゃって... ない！
Should I blame love... no!
今日はデート
Today's a date
彼と10時に待ち合わせしてるの
I'm meeting him at 10 o'clock
Wow wow
今日香りを少し
Today, I changed my perfume a little
変えたこと気付くかしら君は
Will you notice? Will you?
Wow wow
ドクターストップがかかる程
As though I'm following doctor's orders...
「恋落ち」してるわ
...I'm "falling in love."
大好きが止まらない
I can't stop loving you
Oh love me love me love me love me love me do!
Wow wow
カルチャーショックを起こす程
Enough to cause a culture shock,
時代を変えるわ
the times are changing.
スポットライトを浴びる二人
The two of us bathed in the spotlight,
口づけをしましょう
let's kiss!
I love you!
Wahoo!
女の子には
For girls, there is...
秘密の恋のボタンがあるのよ
...a secret love button.
今年の夏は負けない
I won't lose this summer,
去年みたいに弱気じゃない
I'm not timid like last year.
あぁ
Ah...
SUMMER LOVE 胸が騒ぐわ
Summer love, my heart is racing.
SUMMER LOVE
実際恋するだけなら誰でもできる
Actually, anyone can just fall in love,
勇気を持てたら輝くはずよ
but with courage, we should shine.
実際恋愛するのって大変
Actually dating is hard,
見逃せない
but I can't miss it!
夏祭り 手を繋ぎ
Holding hands at the summer festival,
花紙を見上げて
looking up at the fireworks.
「綺麗だね」と 私を見て 君が言う
You look at me and say, "It's beautiful."
浴衣着て
Wearing a yukata,
金魚すくい
scooping goldfish,
私が3匹で
I got three.
なんて恋 夢見てる
I dream of a love like that,
15才
at fifteen.
一人きり イヤフォンで
All alone with my earphones,
音楽聴いている
listening to music.
意味もなく涙とか 出てきちゃう
For no reason, tears start to fall...
あぁ 寂しいよ 寂しいよ
Ah, I'm lonely, I'm lonely,
なぜだか寂しいよ
for some reason, I'm so lonely.
すごい恋 夢見てる
I dream of a wonderful love,
15才
at fifteen.
SUMMER LOVE
ついてくる気が
Do you have any intention to follow me?
あるんでしょうか
I wonder if you do...
ねえ君は
Hey, what about you?
おどおどしてちゃ
If you keep acting timidly,
飲み込まれるよ
you'll get swallowed up,
都会では
here in the city.
愛だ恋だと言い
If you plan to talk about
つもりなら
love and romance,
そうね君
then yes, you...
男らしくて
should be manly,
自信ありげで
full of confidence,
さわやかに
and refreshing.
私達だってそりゃね
Of course, even for us,
甘えたいと思う
we want to be spoiled sometimes.
だけど甘い顔は
But we're not in a position
出来ない立場なの
where we can show a sweet face.
胸元のあいた服を着た私の
Notice my sign as I wear these clothes
サインに気づいて (sain ni kizuite)
with an open neckline,
ねえ
hey...
愛してよ (aishite yo)
Love me!
誰にも負けず
More than anyone else,
愛して愛して愛しすぎて!
love me, love me, love me too much!
安心感
A sense of security,
優越感
a sense of superiority,
それが欲しいの
that's what I want.
抱きしめて
Hold me tight,
生まれたまんまの裸の裸の裸のKISS
with a naked, naked, naked kiss, just as we were born.
この愛が本物と分かればいいの
I just want to know if this love is the real thing.
この愛が本物と分かるように
So I can know if this love is the real thing,
キスして
kiss me.
愛してよ (aishite yo)
Love me!
狂おしいほど愛して愛して愛しすぎて!
Love me, love me, love me so much it drives me crazy!
少しぐらい強引でちょうどいいのよ
Being a little pushy is just right.
抱きしめて
Hold me tight,
生まれたまんまの裸の裸の裸のKISS
with a naked, naked, naked kiss, just as we were born.
この愛が本物と分かればいいの
I just want to know if this love is the real thing.
この愛が本物と分かるように
So I can know if this love is the real thing,
キスして
kiss me.
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ
Hype! Mi Amore!
盛れ！
Hype!
盛れ！ミ・アモーレ
Hype! Mi Amore!
盛れ！
Hype!
盛れ！盛れ！
Hype! Hype!
盛れ！
Hype!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, Mi Amore,
一番の私を見て
look at me at my best.
ありのままだなんて愛してあげない
I won't love you for who you are as you are.
火花みたいな今を
Live this spark-like moment,
今を
right now!
盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！盛れ！
Hype! Hype! Hype! Hype! Hype!
あなたの瞳はフィルター
Your eyes are a filter,
燃えてゆく空気は切な
the burning air is a split second.
もういいなら
If you've had enough,
キレイなまま
while still beautiful,
笑っていたいね
I want to be smiling.
何でも 理想も 一瞬
Anything, even ideals, are just for a moment.
過ごせば 素顔に戻る (sugoseba sugao ni modoru)
Once it passes, we return to our real faces.
だけど あなたにこそ
But it's precisely to you
羽広げ
that I spread my wings.
言葉の角度で
With the angle of my words,
悪魔も手なづける (akuma mo tenazukeru)
taming even the devil.
美しさのせて (utsukushisa nosete)
Carrying beauty,
焼き付けて (yakitsukete)
burn it into your memory!
油断できないわ タッチアップ
I can't let my guard down, touch up!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, Mi Amore,
私をキレイでいさせて (watashi o kirei de isasete)
keep me looking beautiful.
ありのままだなんて愛したくない (ari no mama da nante aishitakunai)
I don't want to love you just as you are.
現実以上でいさせて (genjitsu ijou de isasete)
Let me be better than reality.
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, Mi Amore,
一番の私を見て
look at me at my best.
ありのままだなんて愛してあげない
I won't love you for who you are as you are.
火花みたいな今を
Live this spark-like moment,
今を 盛れ！
right now, hype it up!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, Mi Amore,
あなたをキレイでいさせて (anata o kirei de isasete)
keep yourself looking beautiful.
愛しているからともう騙されない
I won't be fooled anymore just because I love you.
手抜きしないで私達
No cutting corners for us.
Lai, lai, lai, lai, lai...
M-O-R-E M-O-R-E Ah! Woo!
Ah! 盛れ！
Ah! Glam up!
Do do up
今夜は会えそうにないやいやいやい
I don't think we can meet tonight, no, no, no...
不思議と寂しいいやいやいやい
It's strange, but I feel lonely, no, no, no...
背伸びをしてるわけじゃないのに 胸が痛い
I'm not trying to act older than I am, but my heart hurts...
仲間が集まってガキ扱い
When our friends gather, you treat me like a kid.
今すぐ大人になりたいやいやい
I want to grow up right now, yeah, yeah, yeah!
こんなに苦しいのが 初恋ですか？
Is feeling this much pain what first love is?
アーケード
Arcade...
走り抜け
running through it,
信号が青になる
the traffic light turns green.
あの人が
That person,
この時間
at this very hour,
ここを通る
will pass right through here.
ほら
Look!
春紅のスカーレット
The spring crimson scarlet,
我慢なんてできない
I can't hold back anymore!
胸さわぎスカーレット
Heart-throbbing Scarlet...
恋の色が変わる
The color of my love is changing.
Yes, my love
Do do up
週末はみんなわいやいやいやい
Everyone is buzzing on the weekend, yeah, yeah...
なぜなの？ あなたいないやいやいやい
Why is that? You are not here, no, no, no...
こんな日はつまらない そろそろ帰ろうかな
A day like this is boring, maybe I should head home soon.
噂じゃ彼女ができたとか
There's a rumor that you got a girlfriend...
そんなの全く聞きたくない
I don't want to hear anything like that at all!
張り裂けそうな位 頭から離れん
It's so intense that it won't leave my mind.
雨が降る
The rain falls,
週末は
on the weekend,
少し街も静か
even the city is a bit quiet.
このままじゃ
At this rate,
眠れない
I won't be able to sleep,
切なすぎる
it's just too painful.
ああ
Ah,
春紅のスカーレット
the spring crimson scarlet...
ちょっと近づきたい
I want to get a little closer.
胸さわぎスカーレット
Heart-throbbing Scarlet...
恋の虹が光る
The rainbow of love shines.
Yes, my love
ほら
Look!
春紅のスカーレット
The spring crimson scarlet,
我慢なんてできない
I can't hold back anymore!
胸さわぎスカーレット
Heart-throbbing Scarlet...
恋の色が変わる
The color of my love is changing.
Yes, my love
春紅のスカーレット
The spring crimson scarlet,
ちょっと近づきたい
I want to get a little closer.
胸さわぎスカーレット
Heart-throbbing Scarlet...
恋の虹が光る
The rainbow of love shines.
Yes, my love
うわー！
Whoa!
行くぞ！ おー！
Here we go! Oh!
オーマイガー！
Oh my god!
おかえり！
Welcome back!
イェーイ！ はーい！
Yeah! Hi!
キアラ、ハッピーバースデー！
Kiara, happy birthday!
ありがとう！誕生日だけじゃなくて、
Thank you! It's not just my birthday,
2人だけで一緒になるのは初めてだから、もう1つのお祝いなんだよ…
but it's another celebration because this is the first time we're together as just two...
…踊るんだ。
...dancing.
イェーイ！
Yeah!
なんという…なんという出来事でしょう！
What a... what an... occasion!
どうやってこの機会に至ったかは分からないと思うけど、自己紹介をどうぞ！
How we have come to this occasion, you will never know, but please introduce yourself.
お、ハロー！
Oh, what's up!
私は混沌、日々の終わり！ 親友によってネズミの檻に閉じ込められている、
I am Chaos, the end of days! I'm still trapped in the body of a mouse by world's friend,
ハコス・ベールズだよ！見届けてね！
Hakos Baelz from Hololive English - Promise! Witness me!
なんて素晴らしい自己紹介！うわー、私もそんな自己紹介が欲しかったな。
And such a good introduction! Wow, I wish I had such an introduction.
まあ、ようこそ、ようこそ、ようこそ！曲はどうだった？
Well, welcome, welcome, welcome! How did you like the song?
すごく難しかった！そうだよね！
It was so hard! Yeah!
本当に？普通のアイドルダンスを習ったんだけど、これは…
Really? I learned standard idol dances. This...
これは本当に難しい。あ、そうそう。ハロプロではよくあることだけど、でも…
This is so hard. Ah, yes, yes. That happens often in Hello! Project, but...
理解できないよ！
I don't understand!
でも、ダンスレッスンで、このダンスに出てくる色んなジャンルについて教えてくれたよね。
But I remember in the dance lesson, you told me about the different genres of dance that appear in this...
うん、かなり驚いたよ。ハウスが多いんだ。これはかなりハウスっぽいよね。
Yeah, I was quite surprised. There's a lot of house. This is quite housey.
これがハウス？ハウスだよ。オッケー。
This is house? House. Okay.
それから、ロッキングもあるんだ。
And then there's also... there's locking.
あ、これ…ロックって言った？
Oh, this... you said that's rock?
これはロッキング。
This is locking.
あ、ロッキング！あ、ロッキング（Locking）のことね、ロッキング（Rocking）じゃなくて！
Ah, locking! Oh, you meant locking, not rocking!
違う、ロッキング。あ、ロックのダンススタイルがあるのかと思った、オッケー。
No, locking. Oh, I thought there was a rock dance style, okay.
違う、ロッキング。誤解だったね。
No, locking. Misunderstanding.
うん！本当に難しかった！
Yeah! That was so hard!
本当に驚いたよ。ハウスとロッキングが同じダンスに入ってるアイドルダンスなんて、クレイジーだよ！
I swear, I was so surprised. I was like, what kind of idol dance has house and locking in the same dance? That's crazy!
当時は色んなことに挑戦してたんだよね。でも、これは私のお気に入りのアイドルグループ、Berryz工房の曲なんだ。
They were trying all kinds of things back then. But yeah, that's from my favorite idol group, Berryz Kobo.
今の時点ではかなり古い曲なんだけど。でも振付に1箇所だけ、
And it's like a pretty old song at this point. But it has one part in the choreography...
デュオにぴったりだと思った部分があって。だから、あなたと一緒にやりたいと思ったの！
...that I thought would be perfect for like a duo. So I thought, I want to do it with you!
一緒に！
Together!
この部分？
Is this part?
アハハ！
Aha!
すごく楽しかった！本当にやりたかったんだ。ありがとう！イェーイ！
It was so much fun! I really wanted to do it. Thank you! Yay!
オッケー、えっと、私たちのためにちょっとしたゲームも用意したよ。
Okay, um, I have also prepared a little game for us.
ゲーム！
A game!
カメラ！カメラがたくさんあるから、それを活用したいなと思って。
Cameras! There's so many cameras, and I would like to make use of it.
カメラを探すゲームをするよ。
We'll play a game where you have to find the camera.
それで… これが最初に探すカメラ？すごく遠いね。
So... Is this the first camera we're looking for? It's so far.
ここら辺かな？
Maybe it's like here?
あ、そうだ！
Ah, yeah!
はーい！ヤッホー！
Hi! Yahho!
見えた、見えた、見えた！イェーイ！
I see, I see, I see! Yeah!
オッケー、ベイビー、次はあなたが探して。どこにある？
Okay, Bae, you find the next one. Where is that?
そこ？それとも反対側？あ！
Is it there, or is it the opposite? Ah!
私が先に見つける！いや、違う！
I will find it first! No, it's not!
どこ？あ、あれ… まぁ、走り回ってれば、そのうち見つかるよ。
Where is it? Oh, are you... Well, if we continue running around, surely we will find it.
待って、ちょっと待って。
Wait, hold on.
そこだよ！
Right there!
待って、待って、ちょっと待って。見えた、そこだよ！
Wait, wait, wait up. I see it, right there!
あ！ハロー！
Ah! Hello!
はーい！
Hi!
本当に難しかったね。楽しかった。
That was really difficult. That was fun.
次のカメラ。どこでこのカメラを見つけるの？
Next camera. Where did they find these cameras?
見つけたよ！
I see you!
このアングルっていつ使われるの？
When is this angle ever being used?
はーい！こんにちは！
Hi! Konnichiwa!
もう1個、もう1個、もう1個！
One more, one more, one more!
ディスコボールの下。待って、影が見えた。
Under the disco ball. Wait, I saw the shadow.
待って、ディスコボールはこうあるはずだから…
Wait, the disco ball should be like...
お、お、お！え？
Oh, oh, oh! Huh?
これ？違う。
Is it? No.
いや、こう…
No, it's like...
違う、そこじゃない。
No, it's not there.
いや、こう… あ、難しいな… 私これ見てる？
No, it's like... oh, it's hard to... Am I looking at it?
あ！イェーイ！
Ah! Yeah!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
オッケー、オッケー、オッケー。待って、最後？最後？
Okay, okay, okay. Wait, one last one? Last one?
最後。これが最後？
Last one. Is that the last one?
まあ、まあ、これは簡単だね、だって…
Well, well, this one's easy because...
これじゃ挑戦になってないよ！
That's not a challenge!
はーい！イェーイ！
Hi! Yay!
オッケー、オッケー、オッケー、楽しかった！
Okay, okay, okay, that was fun!
さて、さて、さて、さて…
Well, well, well, well...
でも、これで終わりじゃないよ。違う違う、次はどうするの？
This is not the end, though. No, no, no, what are you doing next?
まず、Berryz工房コーナーはもう1曲続くよ、本当に大好きだからね。
First of all, the Berryz Kobo corner will continue for one more song because I love them so much.
お！そして次は…
Oh! And for the next one...
…ゲストが4人いるんだ。
...I have four guests.
4人？！
Four?!
他ならぬ、JUSTICEのみんなだよ。
And they are none other than JUSTICE.
去年、イースターのハロプロカバーソングライブでも来てもらったんだけど、あの時は2Dの、紙みたいな形だったからね。
Because last year, for the Easter Hello Project cover song live, I also had them over, but they were like in 2D, like in a paper form.
おお！
Oh!
だから、今年はみんなを3Dで呼ぼうと思って！
So I thought, well this year I get them all in 3D!
3DのJUSTICE？！
3D JUSTICE?!
うん、ちょっとした衣装を着てもらう予定だよ。
Yeah, and they will be wearing like a little bit of a costume.
コスプレ！あ、コスプレ？
A cosplay! Oh, a cosplay?
そんな感じ。衣装、コスプレ。ミュージックビデオに合わせてね。
Something like that. Costume, cosplay. And it matches the music video.
お、お揃い！
Oh, match!
だから何が違うか注目してね。
So pay attention to what's different.
ということで、残りのショーを楽しんでね…
And with that, I guess, have fun with the rest of the show...
…そして次の曲は、せーの…
...and the next song, which is, se-no...
チャチャシング！
Cha-cha SING!
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Today is goodbye, but my chest hurts
手紙書いていいんだろう？
Should I write a letter?
青春バスガイド
Young bus guide
君はまぶしい
You’re so dazzling
記念に写真とっていいかい？
Can I take a commemorative picture?
青春バスガイド
Young bus guide
一目惚れなんだ
I'm in love at first sight
僕がはじけた
I'm torn apart
とまらない感覚
This unstoppable sensation
これが恋だろう？
Is this love?
君とすれ違う
As I pass by you
いい匂いがした
I smell something pleasant
みんなに優しくするなよ
Don't be nice to everyone
独り占めしたいんだ
I want you all to myself
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, all of it
目線が合う度しびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I become numb
独り占めしたいんだ
I want you all to myself
だけどサヨナラ
But this is goodbye
胸が苦しい
My chest hurts
もっと話していたい
I want to talk with you more
青春バスガイド
Young bus guide
君はまぶしい
You’re so dazzling
マイクに生まれ変わりたい
I want to be reborn as a microphone
あいつもライバル
That person over there is a rival
話しかけてる
She’s coming to talk to you
沸き起こる感覚
This feeling that overcomes me
これがジェラシー
This is jealousy
休憩時間に少し会話できた
During breaks we get to talk a little
まつげがとても長いんだね
You have such long eyelashes
時間よ戻ってくれ
Time, please turn back
最初の日に戻りたい
I want to go back to the first day
君に伝えたいことばかり
I’ve got so much I want to tell you
時間よ戻ってくれ
Time, please turn back
独り占めしたいんだ
I want you all to myself
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, all of it
目線が合うたびしびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I become numb
独り占めしたいんだ
I want you all to myself
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Today is goodbye, but my chest hurts
手紙書いていいんだろう？
Should I write a letter?
青春バスガイド
Young bus guide
君はまぶしい
You’re so dazzling
記念に写真とっていいかい？
Can I take a commemorative picture?
だけどサヨナラ
But this is goodbye
胸が苦しい
My chest hurts
もっと話していたい
I want to talk with you more
青春バスガイド
Young bus guide
君はまぶしい
You’re so dazzling
もう一度君に会いたいよ
I want to see you once more
スッペシャル ジェネレーション！
Special Generation!
どうたらこうたら说明
Saying this and that
言い訳してる
Making excuses
イライラくるなぁ
Don't annoy me
あの子が良いなら
If you like that girl
そっち行けばいいじゃん
Then why don't you go get her
チャラチャラチャラチャラ
Showing off, showing off
シルバー着けて
In silver accessories
フラフラしてる
Tottering about
誰にアピってるの？
Who are you trying to appeal to?
余所見なんて
I won't allow
許さないわよ
Things like looking astray
好きと 好きと 好きと 好きと言いなさい
Say it: you love me, you love me, you love me, you love me
そう この場で
Yeah, say it right here
スッペシャル ジェネレーション
Special generation
運命を信じたい
I want to trust in fate
100万年過ぎたって
Even after a million years pass
この愛はゆるぎない
This love will not be shaken
スッペシャル ジェネレーション
Special generation
嫌いにもなれないわ
I can't even hate you
地下鉄の中だって
While inside the subway
昨日よりも今よりも
More than yesterday, more than right now,
愛して！
love me!
はい！
Hi!
Wow wow yeah!
会ったら会ったで どこに行くでも
When we're together, no matter where we go
ダラダラしてる
It seems like it takes forever
私が決めなきゃ
If I don't make a decision
なんも始まんない
nothing is going to start happening
押したり引いたり
Pushing and pulling
なんて器用にすること出来ない
I just can't seem to get good at it
まっすぐ行くだけよ
I just move straight ahead
誰も彼も 驚くような
It's like everyone is surprised
熱い愛で
With a passionate love
私 私 抱きしめて
embrace me, me
An! hold on my love
スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special generation love
孤独など感じない
I don't feel lonely
池袋過ぎたって
Even if I go through Ikebukuro
この愛は え・い・え・ん
My love will last fo-re-ver
スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special generation love
離れない 離さない
Don't let me, I won't leave you
昨日よりも 今よりも
More so than yesterday, more so than right now
また明日も あ・い・し・て！
Tomorrow, l-o-v-e m-e!
はい！
Hi!
Wow wow yeah!
はい！
Hi!
Wow wow yeah!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special generation love
孤独など感じない
I don't feel lonely
池袋過ぎたって
Even if I go through Ikebukuro
この愛は え・い・え・ん
My love will last fo-re-ver
スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special generation love
離れない 離さない
Don't let me, I won't leave you
昨日よりも 今よりも
More so than yesterday, more so than right now
また明日も あ・い・し・て！
Tomorrow, l-o-v-e m-e!
はい！
Hi!
Wow wow yeah!
はい！
Hi!
スッ！
Su!
ペッ！
Pe!
スッペシャルジェネレーション！
Special Generation!
Thank you so much everybody!
Thank you!
Thank you for coming, thank you for watching!
Bye bye!
Phew!
One more!
Kaboom!
Bye bye!
Announcement, announcement!
Takanashi Kiara Birthday Merchandise 2026!
Here is the banner.
First of all, the big item that is the main character is... body pillow!
I finally did it after so many years of doing merchandise.
I might be running out of ideas a little bit, so
I did something that originally I never thought I would do.
KFP, don't leave me hanging.
Leave me laying on the bed, yeah.
1つ目のアイテムはなんと！一生やらないと思ってたんですけど、やっぱりここまで活動すると、
The first item is... I never thought I'd do this, but after being active for this long,
もう出すししか無い、抱き枕です！
I had no choice but to release it: a body pillow!
いぇーい！
Yay!
Next, we have a really cute plushie set of my kitty-cat kids, Smoothie and Chonkers!
They are so cute and fluffy,
and I can bring them everywhere now, and you should too!
You can hang them on your bag or keys.
２つ目のアイテムはそうですね、私の猫たちのぬいぐるみセットで、
The second item is, as you can see, a plushie set of my cats.
キーチェーンなどとして使えます。
You can use them as keychains and such.
どこにでも連れてってあげてください。
Please take them with you everywhere.
Next one is these badges, but they are a bit unusual because this time they are square
and made from fake leather, so they are a bit squishy.
And of course you can make an ita-bag with this too.
今回のバッジはなんと、フェイクレザーで出来てますし、あと四角だし、変わっておりますが、
These badges are made of fake leather and they're square, which is unique,
もちろんこれでも痛バとか出来たりしますよ。
but of course, you can still use them to make ita-bags.
Last item is the smartphone ring!
Modeled after KFP chickens.
Maybe this way, holding your phone won't be as hard with your wings.
Cute!
最後のアイテムはスマホリング！もちろんKFPモチーフです。
The last item is a phone ring! It's KFP-themed, of course.
Besides that, there is also a voice pack!
I haven't been doing any voice packs these past months,
so make sure to get this one, rare!
そのほかには、久しぶりにボイスもあります。
In addition, we have a voice pack for the first time in a while.
最近あんまり参加してないので、
I haven't really participated lately,
ぜひこの機会にお願いします！
so please take this opportunity to get it!
If you get the full set, then you receive
a Polaroid from me alongside it, and if you are lucky
to get the limited one, then it will be signed by my own hands.
もちろん、いつもの通りフルセットゲットすると、
Of course, as always, if you get the full set,
えー、チェキ付いてきます。
you'll get a photo-style card!
限定版だとキアラのサイン入りですね。
If you get the limited edition, it will have Kiara's signature.
よろしくおねがいします！
Hope you look forward to it!
And one more thing before we end,
I have a...
super awesome song cover coming up right after this!
It's a collaboration with some cuties
that might be familiar to you, IDJ!
Yay, IDJ!
この後は、韓国のVTuberアイドル
Right after this, the premier of the song cover collab
IDJとのコラボ歌ってみたプレミア公開しますので、見てください！
with Korean VTuber idol IDJ will be released, so please check it out!
I will try my best to redirect you into it,
but if it does not work out, please make your way there on your own!
Besides that, thank you so much
for celebrating my birthday today!
I worked so hard on this and I'm really proud.
Please leave a comment and a like,
and if you can, get the merchandise!
In German we say: Auf Wiedersehen!
最後に、今日はお誕生日お祝いに
Lastly, thank you so much
来てくれてありがとうございました！
for coming to celebrate my birthday today!
本当にいろいろ努力してきたのです。
I really put a lot of effort into this.
コメントといいね、そしてもしよかったら
Please leave a comment, a like,
グッズもよろしくお願い致します！
and if you can, the merchandise as well!
ではでは、Auf Wiedersehen!
With that, Auf Wiedersehen!
See you in the song cover!